MANISHA MISHRA

Executive Assistant To Chairman And Managing Director

Personal Details

A Mother

Address

Geeta Colony, Delhi, India 110031

Phone

+91 9958866823

E-mail

mmanisha1825@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/manisha-mishra-3b771b

Skills

Office management

Schedule & calendar planning

Office administration

Travel coordination

Staff Management

Resourceful

Languages

English and Hindi

JOB OBJECTIVE: Executive Assistant skilled at offering high-level administrative support to senior-level staff. Expert in travel management, expense tracking and schedule coordination. Expertly assists executive team using exceptional communication and organizational skills.

Additional Information

• TOTAL WORK EXPERIENCE: (12+ Years)

Presently working as an Executive Assistant to Chairman and Managing Director in SMC Investments and Advisors Ltd. since October'17 (5 years to till date)

Worked as an Executive Assistant to Director in Construction based Industry since June'16 (1 Year 2 months).

1 Year of working experience in Real Estate.

3 Years of working experience in HR and Admin. Department.

• Annual CTC: 10.80 Lacs

Work History

2017-10 -Current

Executive Assistant to the Chairman and MD

SMC Global Securities Ltd., Delhi

- Maintains executive's schedules and communications of key company executives, prioritizing emails and phone calls, gathering documents to prepare for meetings and coordinating travel arrangements
- Updated spreadsheets and databases to track, analyze and report on performance and sales data.
- Organized and coordinated conferences and monthly meetings.
- Responded to emails and other correspondence to facilitate communication and enhance

business processes.

- Processed travel expenses and reimbursements for executive team and senior management group.
- Led staff and vendors in providing high level of service for owner and guests.
- Maintain accurate and balanced calendars. Greeted arriving
- visitors, determined nature and purpose of visit and directed individuals to appropriate destinations.
- Filed paperwork and organized computer-based information.
- Handled logistics, catering, agendas and travel arrangements for meeting and event planning for board of directors, president and executive vice president.
- Took notes and dictation of meetings.

Executive Assistant to the Director

Growever Infra Corp

- Maintains executive's appointment schedule by planning and scheduling meetings, conferences and travel
- Represents executive by attending meetings in executive's absence, and note key points for discussion.
- Handled confidential and sensitive information with discretion and tact.

Assistant Sales Manager

Aadhar Group

- Managed and developed sales team.
- Directed sales support staff in administrative tasks to help sales reps close deals.
- Prepared sales presentations for clients showing success and credibility of products.
- Resolved problems with high-profile customers to maintain relationships and increase return customer base.

Front Desk Office Manager

Bhargava Phytolab, Formerly R.S. Bhargava Pharmacy

• (making interview calls, scheduling interviews,

2016-06 -2017-10

2015-03 -2016-04

2013-07 -2014-11

- appointment letters and allied activities). Answered multiline phone system to respond to inquiries and transfer calls to correct departments and personnel.
- Kept accounts in balance and ran daily reports to verify totals.
- Controlled cash and credit card payment transactions at front desk to successfully reduce errors.

Front Desk Receptionist

2011-10 -2013-04 Rachna Sagar Pvt. Ltd, Old

1.5 Years of working experience in HR and, Based Publishers Of Educational Books) as a Receptionist and Voice Artist for Books & CDs

- Maintained files and records by implementing effective filing systems that boosted efficiency and organization.
- Answered multi-line phone system and transferred callers to appropriate department or staff member.
- Maintained organized and clean front office area to create professional and welcoming environment for visitors and employees.
- Completed data entry and filing to keep records updated for easy retrieval.
- Answered questions and addressed, resolved, or escalated issues to management personnel to satisfy customers.

Education

2006-04 - 2007-03	12th Passed: Arts And Humanities
	Lady Irwin School - Delhi
2005-04 -	10th
2006-03	Lady Irwin School (CBSE Board) - NEW DELHI
2009-04 -	Bachelor of Arts
2011-03	Shridhar University, Rajasthan - Rajasthan